[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fry up is another name for the traditional breakfast of what country?", "correct_answer": "England", "incorrect_answers": ["Norway", "Sweden", "The Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first vice president from the Republican Party?", "correct_answer": "Hannibal Hamlin", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Jefferson", "John Tyler", "John Adams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When expressed by a medical term, containing the word phobia, which one of these has the most letters?", "correct_answer": "the fear of long words", "incorrect_answers": ["the fear of kidney disease", "the fear of the number 666", "the fear of foreign languages"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Popeyes franchising began in 1976.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the following medications for anxiety, which is potentially addictive?", "correct_answer": "Ativan (lorazepam)", "incorrect_answers": ["Prozac (fluoxetine)", "Buspar (buspirone)", "Effexor (venlafaxine)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the Chihuahua cheese created?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Argentina", "Portugal", "Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This mini-series, starring Native American actors Gordon Tootoosis and Gerald Auger, was produced by Steven Spielberg and got a Golden Globe nomination in 2006.", "correct_answer": "Into the West", "incorrect_answers": ["Dances With Wolves", "Powwow Highway", "Dreamkeeper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Excluding Englands cities, which city built the first subway in Europe?", "correct_answer": "Budapest", "incorrect_answers": ["Rome", "Paris", "Barcelona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rafflesia, a parasitic plant found in southeastern Asia, has flowers, which smell like what?", "correct_answer": "Rotting meat", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweet perfume", "Mushrooms", "Garlic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is especially rich in omega-3 and omega-6 fatty acids?", "correct_answer": "Flax seed", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown sugar", "Chicken", "Wheat gran"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In most U.S. casinos counting the cards even mentally is illegal.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This delicacy, typical for \u2018The Country of the Rising Sun\u2019, usually only consists of thinly sliced raw seafood, dipping sauce and garnish.", "correct_answer": "Sashimi", "incorrect_answers": ["Moussaka", "Tsatsiki", "Vaho"]}]